Yuito!
유이토
It's not just New Himuka,
뉴히무카 뿐만 아니라
even Seiran is full of evil!
세이란도 문제가 많아
They are using human brains to make drugs!
사람의 뇌로 약을 만들었다고
But without the ampoule, I can't save my sister.
그래도 그 앰풀이 없으면 언니를 구할 수 없게 돼
This is 2nd Lieutenant Sumeragi's brainwave while he was using his power.
이건 스메라기 소위 님이 초뇌능력을 사용할 때의 뇌파입니다
And when we compare it with the Kunad Gate's readings...
쿠나도 게이트와 비교해보면
Are you sure you've made no mistake?
확실한 거 맞아?
We can't be certain for the time being.
아직 단언하기는 이르나…
The Kunad Gate and Yuito's power...
쿠나도 게이트와… 유이토의 초뇌능력이라…
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♫A crime in reality♫
현실의 Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven's sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
거짓을 받아들여
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
영원한 환상은 점점 사라져가
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
결코 완벽하지 않아 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
뒤돌아 걸어오는 소녀는
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
순간 이 세상에 기적을 남겨
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
최고의 게임을 찾았어
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I've never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
난 언제부터 이런 세상이 질렸던 걸까
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won't be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
더는 해치고 싶지 않기에 나를 희생해
THE TRAITOR YUITO
(반역자 유이토)
The people who suggested for Seiran to build that facility
그리고 세이란에 그 연구소를 만들도록 제의한 사람이
were Karen and I.
바로 나와 카렌이다
Alice was in there, am I right?
앨리스가 거기에 있다는 거죠?
Yes.
그래
She is still in her Other form.
여전히 괴이의 모습을 하고 있다
We knew the technology would be abused.
분명 마음껏 남용하겠지만
But we persuaded Seiran into
세이란시를 부추겨
building the facility.
연구소를 건축하게 했다
All that just to protect Alice.
앨리스를 구하기 위해서였지
I knew my action was foolish.
바보 같은 짓이란 거 안다
What is going on in this country?
나라가 진짜 미친 거 아닌가요?
You conducted human experiment in Suoh,
스오에서 인체 실험을 하고
and then you used human brains to experiment on Other in Seiran...
세이란에서 사람의 뇌로 괴이를 연구하다니
That's all the more reason to take action as soon as possible.
그러니까 최대한 빨리 움직여야 해
Major General Fubuki, what is your action plan?
계획해둔 작전이라도 있으십니까? 후부키 연대장님
Nagi witnessed Naomi's metamorphosis.
나기는 나오미가 변이된 걸 목격했고
For research purposes, his memory from that moment has been taken.
연구진은 연구를 위해 나기의 기억을 빼앗아갔다
They took his memory during the rehabilitation?
인격 교정과 함께… 기억을 가져갔군요…
After acquiring the data from Nagi's memory,
나기의 기억 데이터를 얻은 뒤
we will spread it to all people in this country via Arahabaki.
아라하바키를 이용해 전 국민에게 전송했다
I have access to the secure site of Arahabaki.
난 이미 아라하바키 제어층 진입 허가를 받았다
I understand.
그렇군요
Where is the data on Nagi's memory?
그럼 나기의 기억 데이터는 어디에 있는 겁니까?
They took his memory and damaged his brain.
기억을 빼앗을 때 대뇌가 손상되었겠네
The data is kept there.
데이터가 저기에 있어
Nagi underwent rehabilitation over there.
나기가 저기에서 인격 교정을 받았으니
That's where they keep the files.
데이터가 분명 저기에 있을 거야
Nagi could be in there as well.
나기가… 저기에 있을지도 몰라
It's very likely so.
그럴 가능성이 높아
Are you sure, Hanabi?
진짜 괜찮겠어? 하나비
I get it.
알아
But my father and uncle might know something.
하지만 삼촌과 아빠가 뭔가 알고 있을지도 몰라
I feel just as confused as you are.
나도 너랑 같은 기분이야
I've jammed the alarm system.
경위 시스템 교란에 성공했어
Is the information we got from Major General Fubuki useful?
연대장님이 준비한 데이터가 쓸모 있는 거야?
Yes, it is.
아주 유용해
I got it.
알겠어
Everyone, let's go.
같이 가보자
Alice is in here, Fubuki.
앨리스가 여기에 있다는 거지? 후부키
Arashi, Major General Karen wants everyone to gather up.
아라시, 카렌 연대장님이 소집 명령 내렸어
He wants all members of the Kasane Platoon present.
카사네 소대는 전부 집결하도록 해
I got the reports from our research facility.
연구시설의 보고를 받았다
You let Yuito and his team escape.
유이토 일행을 일부러 보내준 건가?
I told you, I am not entirely on board with Seiran's doing.
난 세이란을 백 프로 인정하지는 않는다고 했다
To turn those metamorphosed into Other back to normal again,
넌 단지 변이된 인간들을 되돌리기 위해
you allow Seiran to continue their research on weaponizing Other.
세이란이 괴이를 무기로 연구하도록 내버려둔 거지
Yes.
그렇다
Even with the slightest mistake,
뜻밖의 실수라도 생기면
those from Seiran will suspect you.
세이란에서 어떻게 생각할 것 같나?
Please consider the risk before you take any action.
다음에는 먼저 생각이란 걸 해보도록
Naomi is there. Are you sure you can save her?
나오미를 진짜 구할 수 있는 거 맞아?
She seems to despise that drug.
그 뒤로 나오미는 약을 거절하고 있습니다
Well, that's for sure.
하긴
Who would like drinking that stuff?
그런 약을 좋아할 사람이 있을 리가 있나?
Even so, there is no other way to save Naomi at the moment.
하지만 아직은 나오미를 구할 유일한 방법이다
By that, you mean we must force her to take medicine against her will.
그러니까 나오미의 의지와 상관없이 계속해서 약을 먹여야 한다는 거네
That's all he would do.
이 남자라면 그럴 수밖에 없겠지
Are you done with the speech?
얘기 끝났습니까?
No, there's one more concern.
아니, 한가지 더
We noticed a certain link with the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트에 대해 새로운 발견이 있다
Kasane, you must be interested.
넌 아마 흥미가 돋을 테지, 카사네
Mom, hurry up! Over there!
엄마, 빨리 와, 이쪽이야
-Yuito, it's too dangerous. Don't go there. -Hurry up!
-유이토, 위험하니까 가지 마 -빨리
He has always been a stubborn kid.
어려서부터 말을 안 듣는 녀석이었지
But this time, I must make him obey
이번만큼은 반드시 스메라기 가문의 일원으로서
as a member of the Sumeragi family.
명령에 복종하게 할 거야
Yes, I'll be right back.
나야, 지금 바로 돌아가지
Bring 2nd Lieutenant to the headquarters.
스메라기 소위를 본부로 불러와
Yes.
예
What is it?
무슨 일이야?
Sir, we lost contact with 2nd Lieutenant Sumeragi.
스메라기 소위와 연결이 안 됩니다
The comms and brain talk didn't work.
통신 시스템과 브레인 토크 모두 안됩니다
Where is he now?
소위가 어디에 있나?
We have no idea.
모르겠습니다
It's not his shift now, so we didn't give him any mission.
지금은 근무 시간이 아니라서 임무를 파견하지 않았습니다
Find him.
당장 찾아내
You are allowed to use the surveillance system.
감시 시스템을 사용해도 좋다
Yes.
예
What is going on?
어떻게 된 거지?
I see. A new security measure for Arahabaki.
그렇군, 새로운 아라하바키 안전조치 계획이라
This place doesn't look like a data center.
데이터를 저장할만한 곳은 아닌 것 같은데
I don't see any research equipment either.
연구 설비도… 전혀 안 보여
We must search every inch of the ground.
철저히 수사할 수밖에
I'll buy you some time, run while you can!
내가 차단할 테니까 얼른 도망가
Nagi...
나기…
He stayed to fight for us.
우리를 위해 끝까지 남아서 싸웠어
That was the only way back then.
그때는 그럴 수밖에 없었지
I want to rescue Nagi.
나기를 구해야겠어…
Yuito, you are as kind as ever.
넌 여전히 다정하구나, 유이토
I knew you would come back.
역시 다시 올 줄 알았어
After all, we are good friends.
우리는 친구이니까
Nagi...
나기…
Major General Fubuki, please come with us.
후부키 연대장님, 저희와 함께 가주시죠
Chief Sumeragi wishes to have a word.
스메라기 본부장님께서 찾으십니다
He seems different now.
느낌이 달라졌어
Did they force him to undergo another rehabilitation?
설마 더 강력한 인격 교정을 받은 건가?
This can't be...
어떻게 이럴수가
Personality rehabilitation?
인격교정?
Rehabilitation is for traitors of New Himuka, like you!
교정받아야 할 인간은 뉴히무카 정부에 반항하는 너희 아니야?
Stop it, Nagi!
나기, 멈춰
Yuito!
유이토
Team!
다들
It's happening again.
또 시작이네
I must stay conscious!
지금 의식이 끊기면 안 돼…
Yuito!
유이토…
Freeze, traitors.
반역자들은 들어라
I'll demonstrate the punishment for treason
이 녀석을 통해
using this kid over here.
나라를 배신한 결과를 보여주지
It's been proven the Kunad Gate was linked to Yuito's brain power.
쿠나도 게이트가 유이토의 초뇌능력과 연관되어있다는 것이 사실이네
So the future Yuito was right after all.
오십 년 뒤의 유이토가 한 얘기가 진짜였어
So Yuito was the cause.
그렇다면 역시…
Is killing Yuito the only solution we have?
유이토를 죽일 수밖에 없는 건가?
Kasane, don't you have something to say?
뭐라도 좀 말해봐, 카사네
Nothing I say changes anything.
얘기해도 소용없어
We'll decide whether it's worth it or not!
소용없다니? 결정권은 우리한테 있어
You don't get to decide all on your own.
넌 너무 독단적이야
You are not cute, and not to mention a show-off!
귀엽지도 않고 잘난 체 하지
You've been this way since you joined the force.
입대했을 때부터 그랬어
But you are decisive.
하지만 신속한 결단력이 있어
You complete every task with perfection.
해야 할 일은 완벽하게 처리하지
On that regard, I'll give you credit.
그런 면에서 난 널 인정해
That's right.
그래
I acknowledge your strength.
난 네 실력을 인정해
That is why we fight for you.
그래서 지금까지 너랑 함께하는 거야
So at least have more faith in us.
그러니까 우리를 조금이라도 믿어봐
Tell us what you have in mind.
네 생각을 전부 말해보란 말이야
We'd love to know what's bothering you.
네가 뭘 고민하는지 알아
A thought is only pointless
얘기해도 소용없다는 건
when you keep it to yourself.
고민이 있지만 혼자 참고 있는 거잖아
Just tell us what it is.
말해봐
We have the right to know.
우리도 알 권리는 있으니까
He's right.
맞아
We are a team after all.
우리는 같은 소대잖아
Sorry.
미안해…
Are you still not going to tell us?
여전히 얘기하기 싫은 거야?
That's not the case.
아니야
I'm sure I could give you a clear explanation,
제대로 설명할 자신이 없어
so I thought it would be futile to even try.
그래서 소용없다고 한 거야
So you have my apology.
이 일에 대해서는 미안하게 생각해
I see.
그런 뜻이었어?
Then just tell us.
그럼 그냥 말하면 되지
Sorry.
미안해
I apologize for not being able
이건 그냥 말하지 못해서
to give you a clear explanation.
모두의 오해를 산 것에 대한 사과야
So...
그래서…
I know that.
그런 건 나도 알아
All right.
됐어
Stop arguing.
그만 싸워
Please tell us.
말해봐
Killing Yuito to prevent the destruction of our world
유이토가 죽지 않으면 세계는 파멸돼
could be our only solution.
이건 진짜인 것 같아
I felt it at the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트에서 느껴졌어…
You saw it too. That giant hole is growing and slowly consuming the world.
점차 커지면서 세상을 삼키는 저 블랙홀을 너도 봤을 거야
And according to Karen,
그리고 카렌이 했던 말도
he knew I had been to the future.
카렌은 내가 미래에 다녀온 걸 알고 있어
And there has been scientific evidence
과학적인 증명까지 결합해보면
that proves the link between Yuito and the Kunad Gate.
유이토와 쿠나도 게이트의 관계는
That's an undeniable fact.
부인할 수 없는 사실이기도 해
Even so...
하지만…
So your conclusion is that
그래서 얻은 결론이
we must kill Yuito to save the world.
유이토를 죽이는 거야?
But you're hesitating
하지만 망설이게 되는 거지?
because you think there could be another way.
혹시 다른 해결 방법은 있지 않을까 해서
It's the same with Naomi.
나오미 문제도 그렇고
I doubt we can trust Karen or Seiran.
카렌과 세이란은 믿을만한 상대가 아니야
That research facility is up to no good.
연구진도 결코 좋은 놈들이 아니고
But we can't save Naomi by simply waiting here.
여기에 있어야만 나오미를 구할 수 있다는 확신도 없어
Let's figure out a plan together.
아무튼 함께 고민해보자
She's right. We are comrades who trust each other.
맞아, 우리는 서로를 믿어야 해
-Sorry. -Wrong answer, Kasane.
-미안 -또 단어 사용이 틀렸지? 카사네
There should be a different reply.
이런 상황에서는 다른 말을 해야지
Well... Everyone...
저기… 다들…
Thank you.
고마워
Fubuki...
후부키가…
I see. Keep tracking them.
그래? 계속 추적해
I'll be going now.
난 갈게
Yuito, you must be scared right now.
유이토, 많이 무서워?
The examination is over.
검사는 이미 끝났어
Come, look at me.
자, 엄마한테로 와
Don't cry, it's over.
울지 마, 이제 괜찮아
Mom!
엄마
Our test subject is 2nd Lieutenant Sumeragi.
피험자 유이토 스메라기 소위
The subject is 16 years old. Registration number SY567369.
16세, 등록 번호는 SY567369
Remark: "Savior of the Nation."
비고 "구국 영웅"
Use your power.
초뇌능력을 사용하십시오
Use your power to break free from the bindings.
초뇌능력으로 잠금장치에서 벗어나십시오
Brain power control system is functioning.
초뇌능력 제어 시스템은 정상입니다
The brain power control system is functioning.
이제 처치를 시작하겠습니다
Wait, hold on.
잠시만요
What is this place? Who are you?
여기는 어디이며 당신은 누구인가요?
Don't you remember me?
저를 못 알아보시겠습니까?
We've met many times in the past.
예전에 이곳에서 자주 뵈었습니다
More precisely speaking, I had met you 17 times 11 years ago.
정확히 11년 전에 17차례 만났습니다
You've met me?
저와… 만났었다고요?
It's normal you don't remember people you met in the hospital.
병원에서 만났던 사람을 기억 못할 수도 있죠
But as a precaution, I must validate the test subject's condition.
하지만 혹시 모르니 피험자의 상태를 체크하겠습니다
Do you remember staying in this hospital?
이 병원에 입원한 적 있으시죠?
There are some differences in the test subject's memory.
피험자의 기억에 오차가 있나봅니다
That's not important. Where are my friends?
그것보다 제 동료들은 어디에 있어요?
The lowered psionic hormone fixation rate could be the cause.
아마도 초감각 자극 호르몬이 일정하게 떨어지기 때문인 것 같습니다
According to the data,
데이터에 의하면
you discovered your power 11 years ago.
11년 전에 갑자기 초뇌능력을 얻게 되었고
It was different from the modification process that of a Bell Pepper.
일반적인 벨 페퍼를 개조하는 과정과는 다릅니다
Bell Pepper?
벨 페퍼?
The test subject doesn't remember ever being a Bell Pepper.
피험자는 벨 페퍼였던 때의 기억을 잃어버린듯 합니다
I think using the brain power
매번 초뇌능력을 사용할 때마다
will accumulate a certain amount of damage to the subject's brain.
대뇌가 받은 손상이 누적되면서
That could be the cause of his memory loss.
갑자기 기억을 잃는 증상이 나타난 것으로 보입니다
What is going on?
이게 어떻게 된 거죠?
Was I a Bell Pepper?
제가 벨 페퍼라고요?
For those born as Bell Peppers,
벨 페퍼로 태어난 국민에게 진행된
the success rate after the drug administration test is 0.5%.
투약 실험이 성공할 확률은 0.5%입니다
Only a handful of people will become users of powers.
극 소수의 인간만이 후천적 초뇌능력자의 뇌력이 발견됩니다
Only 0.2% of those with acquired powers
그리고 후천적 초뇌능력자 중 0.2%만
have abnormally strong powers.
일반인과 다른 초 강력한 능력을 얻을 수 있습니다
But your situation is unique and unprecedented.
하지만 지금 이런 상태인 자는 아마 피험자가 처음일 겁니다
For study purpose of our future plans for the Bell Peppers,
향후 벨 페퍼 대책을 위한 참고 자료가 필요하므로
I think it's necessary to conduct a dissection to extract the brain data.
피험자의 대뇌를 해부해 브레인 데이터를 채취해야 하니
Requesting permission to dissect the subject.
해부 허가를 수락해주십시오
Yuito!
유이토
Hanabi!
하나비
Major General Fubuki, why are you here?
후부키 연대장님, 왜 그러세요?
The program I gave you
너희 프로그램에
was modified to stream live images.
감시 영상 전송 기능을 설치했다
You saved all of us.
덕분에 우리도 살았어요
What about Nagi? Where is he?
나기, 나기는요?
We don't know.
몰라
We couldn't find his memory data either.
기억 데이터도 못 찾았어
Yuito, are you all right?
유이토, 너 괜찮아?
Great.
다행이다
Sorry, everyone. Thanks for saving me.
다들 미안하고 고마워
You've always saved me from danger.
내가 여러모로 도움을 받네
Let's leave this place.
얼른 가지
Our mission here
우리가 여기에 있다는 거
has been informed to the OSF.
토벌군이 이미 알아버렸다
Their soldiers will be here soon.
분명 추격병을 보낼 것이다
I got the escape route from Major General Fubuki.
이미 후부키 연대장님으로부터 탈출 노선을 알아냈어
The Others are coming this way.
괴이가… 몰려오고 있어
We must leave now.
얼른 여기를 벗어나야 한다
I'll handle the Others.
괴이는 내가 처리할 테니
But...
하지만…
Take this.
이걸 가져가
What is it?
이건…
It's Arahabaki's password.
아라하바키 암호다
It's a terminal that can only show the password once.
암호는 오직 한 번만 볼 수 있다
Well, you should go.
자, 어서 떠나라
I am a Septentrion.
난 셉텐트리온이니
I can clear this horde with no problem.
혼자서도 충분하다
Major General Fubuki.
후부키 연대장님
It's time to leave, Yuito.
얼른 가야 해, 유이토
Good luck.
부디 주의하세요
Brother!
형
Yuito.
유이토
You've become a traitor as well.
너도 이제 반역자다
Could it be...
설마…
"TRAITOR YUITO SUMERAGI WANTED" The hero of our nation Yuito Sumeragi
(반역자 유이토 스메라기 지명 수배) 국구 영웅 유이토 스메라기 소위가
has committed treason and is now wanted by the government.
반역자로 되어 정부에서 지명 수배를 내렸습니다
2nd Lieutenant Yuito and his team infiltrated a government facility
유이토 스메라기 소위가 부하들과 함께 정부 시설에 잠입해
to conduct a sabotage mission, but their mission was uncovered.
시설을 파괴하던 중 발각되었습니다
As of now...
현재…
Why?
왜 이렇게 된 거야?
Soon enough, you won't be able to enter Suoh.
넌 곧 있으면 스오에 진입할 수 없게 될 거다
Well, Yuito?
어떠냐? 유이토
Would you come to Seiran?
세이란으로 올 것이냐?
Seiran will welcome you and your team as ally.
세이란은 너희를 아군으로 받아줄 거다
You are asking me to join hands with people who use human brains for Other experiment!
사람의 뇌로 괴이를 연구하는 놈들이랑 손잡으라는 건가요?
New Himuka wanted to create stronger brain powers,
뉴히무카는 더 강력한 초뇌능력을 만들기 위해
so they conducted human metamorphosis experiments.
인간의 변이 실험을 실시했다
Suoh was New Himuka's central city.
그리고 스오는 뉴히무카의 중심도시다
You are both just as wicked and insane!
양쪽 모두 비뚤어졌어요, 전부 잘못됐다고요
What do you propose then?
그럼 어떡할 건데?
Are you going to flee to Togetsu instead?
종교국인 토게츠에 도망이라도 갈 건가?
They are an autonomous region.
거긴 종교자치구다
Perhaps even the greatest sinners
외부에 극악무도한 자라고 알려져도
would be accepted there.
아마 받아주겠지
Togetsu?
토게츠…
He has a point. The government wouldn't attack Togetsu to get to us.
뉴히무카가 토게츠에 손대지 않는 건 확실해
They are an independent city.
그곳은 독립된 도시이니까
Brother, did you came all the way here to tell us that?
형, 혹시 이걸 알려주러 온 거야?
I was merely passing by.
겸사겸사
Take this with you if you're going to Togetsu.
토게츠에 가려거든 이걸 들고 가
-I'm not going to... -Whether it's human blood
-싫어요… -사람의 피가 들었든
or human brain,
뇌가 들었든
this thing will keep you alive.
살아가려면 이걸 먹어야 하지
Otherwise,
안 먹으면
you will lose both your memory and your power.
기억과 초뇌능력을 전부 잃게 될 테니까
This ampoule will delay the symptoms.
이 앰풀은 그 증상을 늦춰줄 거다
You must take it whether you like it or not.
먹기 싫어도 먹을 수밖에 없다
Brother!
형
Hurry up! The soldiers are coming!
빨리 움직여, 추격병이 오고 있어
Karen...
카렌…
They should be on the move by now.
이제 움직일 때가 됐겠네
Are you worried about something again?
혼자 또 뭘 고민하는 거야?
I told you, we could figure it out as a team.
함께 고민하기로 했잖아
Kyoka.
쿄카
Is it about Yuito?
유이토 때문에 그래?
Or is it about Naomi?
아니면 나오미?
Perhaps it's both?
둘 다 고민하는 거지?
Are you going to stay in Seiran and follow Karen's leadership?
진짜 카렌과 함께 세이란에 남을 생각이야?
Kasane.
카사네
Why don't we go to Togetsu instead?
토게츠에 가지 않을래?
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
운명의 지시 따윈 필요 없어
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
분명 고쳐질 거라 믿으니까
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
앞으로도 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 말이야
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
눈부시게 빛나는 태양이 막을 내리고
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
세상의 끝에서 뭘 기다리고 있는걸까
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
♫Who can shake us♫
누가 우리를 위협해
♫Who can define us♫
누가 우리 대신 결정해
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
이건 우리만의 스토리야
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
네 마음속 미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
JOURNEY TO TOGETSU
(토게츠행)